Phobthee, you need to lead our team to that place
and detain important members for negotiation.
The leader should be a person who is close to Kitti,
Captain Phobthee.
If they break in, you can shoot them all.
Phob!
Go to hell!
Your Highness!
- Your Highness.
- Phob.
Your Phob is right here with you.
And I won't leave your side, ever.
Captain Phobthee?
Why are you here for?
I don’t have to visit him because of work merely,
perhaps I can visit him when I miss him.
This is profit from your first coal mining business' investment, Your Highness.
I got this much profit from the first month?
I think it's because of your luck.
I am hesitating if I should
invest some more.
I want to gain more profits.
You would be stupid if you didn't invest more.
Here, put this money into my share and I will find more to invest.
I still have money from the ministry's budget.
Oh wow!
You're so brilliant.
I can guarantee you that by June,
we both will be so wealthy.
Come on, cheers!
Everyone will finally realize
that I didn't have to do well in school like Tin and Phob,
still I can make more money than they can.
And my dad will finally praise me.
Let's cheers again!
Let's get rich!
You used work as an excuse
to be around my son all the time.
If that's the case, what are you going to do about it?
Phob!
You need to stop being around Tinnakorn already.
Let him go.
I am not a servant in your palace.
I don’t have to do what you say.
Also,
Prine Tinnakorn
risked his life to save mine.
He was so brave to save me.
You can't expect me to leave him just like that.
Chat?
Whose car is this?
This is my car, Grandma.
I invested in mining business with my friend.
I thought that I'd buy a small car but
I made a lot of profit so I decided to buy the same model and color as my dad's.
Wonderful.
This one is for you.
For me?
- That's right.
- Thanks, honey.
Thank you so much. I wish you big success in your business.
- Thank you. Hey, Aum.
- Yes?
Tell the servants to meet me in the main building.
I have some gifts for everyone.
Sure, Your Highness. Thank you.
Well done.
Dad?
I have invested
in mining business with my friends and I gained a lot of profit.
So I bought a new car
it is the same model and the same color as yours.
Isn't she pretty?
Are you sure that it is from the business investment?
It wasn't from your gambling money? Don't drag us to your problems.
Vasin,
don't be too harsh on him,
okay?
- Aum?
- Yes, Your Highness.
If Tinnakorn is here, tell him to see me.
Yes, Your Highness.
My dad has never cared about me.
He has never praised me, he only cares about Tinnakorn.
Come on, don't be sad.
He just came back from work, he must be exhausted.
Okay?
Grandma, you have to see it.
I will make a lot of money
and I will show my dad that I can do well in my life.
I will bring good reputation to the family.
I will, I can't wait to see it.
I wish your dream comes true.
- I love you the most.
- I love you, too.
Let's try it on. I want to see it.
Aum told me that you wanted to see me.
Is everything okay?
Have a seat.
A nephew of my colleague will come back from England last week.
I am looking for a right job for him.
I think this is a good opportunity
that he can replace you at work.
What do you mean?
You need to resign,
and stay home.
while I'm looking for a new position for you.
A new position?
A new position that I don't have to be involved with Phobthee?
That's right.
Why are you doing this?
You need to ask yourself.
You took a bullet for him.
You wanted me to let Chat shot him to death?
Tinnakorn,
you know the real reason why you saved him.
It wasn't because of humanity.
But it was because you didn't forget him.
You should have forgotten all about him.
You should have stopped loving him or thinking about him.
You need to protect the family's honor.
The family's honor?
Why does the family's honor feel so heavy on my shoulders?
I can't even
think about him
- or keep him in my memories.
- Tinnakorn!
Actually, if you want me to forget all about this,
there is another way.
What is it?
You can just kill me.
Tinnakorn!
My prince, where are you?
Where are you?
Are you here?
My prince, where are you?
There you are! I found you!
Oh my! You found me!
No matter where you are
I will always find you.
Phob.
Your Highness.
Oh my gosh!
You don't like it?
It's too cold.
I saw you working hard so I brought you some water,
to freshen you up.
Thank you.
Is it cold enough?
Hey! Phob!
Oh, it stays.
Hey!
Give me your money!
Hurry up, you want to die?
Phob!
- Hey!
- Phob!
Watch out!
Let's go, hurry!
Phob!
Are you hurt? Did they do anything to you?
I'm fine.
Phob! Your blood?
Phob!
I'm fine.
You're safe now.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You should go.
But I think I should…
- I should drive you back to your palace.
- No, you can't.
I can go back tomorrow myself.
But right now, you should go.
- But..
- You should go.
Get home safe, okay?
Is everything okay? Did you forget something?
No, I didn't.
I just think
that I should stay here with you.
It's totally fine, you should go.
- But it's dangerous…
- You need to go.
You need to leave.
Go!
Just go!
Leave me alone!
You need to go! Why did you come back?
Why can't I stay away from you?
I thought that if we never met again,
it would have been easier than this.
I could just see you in my dream.
I could just miss you.
Now you're standing right in front of me. What do you expect me to do?
How do you expect me to forget you?
I used to think that way.
But no matter how long it takes,
I can never forget you.
My heart
always belongs to you.
And it will always belong to you
forever,
it will never change.
Hi,
you're up?
We shouldn't have done this, Phob.
You're right.
We shouldn't have done this.
But I will do this.
Phob!
Stop it.
Do you know
how long I've waited for this moment?
Phob.
Yeah?
I need to tell you something.
I heard about
people trying to transform the national regime.
Have you ever heard of this?
What's the matter?
You can't be around these people.
It is dangerous
and you could be the suspect.
Do you hear me?
Tin.
Dad?
Where have you been all night?
- I…
- About last night,
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize to me.
You've sacrificed your happiness for the family's honor.
I shouldn't force you like that.
Instead, I should have been more understanding.
From now on, I won't be involved
with your work anymore.
Dad?
Please forgive me.
Do you like the house?
Yeah.
Let's take a look inside.
This house belongs to Janthorn's relative. It's for rent.
It is isolated.
Don't worry,
nobody can find us here.
We can meet here, what do you think?
If my dad finds out about this,
he must be so mad.
Take it one day at a time.
You know that my dad expects me to take care of the palace.
He loves and worships his family more than anything.
So he puts all the burden
on his son's shoulders?
Don't say that.
It is my job.
You may not have to bear the burden all by yourself in the future.
What do you mean?
Well,
I mean that
I can help with your burden
and I can help with the thing that bothers you.
Sounds good?
I guess.
Now we have cotton rose tree at our house, Phob.
Phob!
- Come on, let me do it.
- No.
Just find something to shield me from oil, hurry.
Put it down.
- Be careful.
- Phob!
Let me taste it.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
How is it?
- Is it good?
- It's good.
If you like it, then you should try this.
- So good.
- I knew it.
I think I cooked it so well. I'm so sure.
Among four dishes, which one is your most favorite?
My most favorite?
I think it is…
That's enough.
Let me try.
- You think this is good?
- Yeah.
You sure?
My prince, come here.
- What is it?
- Come on, hurry.
- Hurry!
- It's here.
- Phob!
The cotton rose that we planted is blooming.
Tinnakorn.
Yes?
Are you leaving the city again?
That's right.
Why do you have to visit the country so often?
You've been gone for a month.
I'm not sure about that.
You should get going, I wont' disturb you.
See you later.
Do you think it will work?
Don't worry.
The students from France planned the whole thing so well.
The national regime transformation
will get done easily.
What are they going to do with the royal family?
They will be executed
and their assets will be confiscated.
Is that so?
Did the two soliders confess about who ordered them?
Not yet, Your Highness.
But I contacted the head of police department already.
If they spilled the names of their underground leaders,
the arrest warrant will be issued.
They were so drunk and they spilled the plan.
They claimed that they were progressive
but they made a stupid mistake.
We need to tackle the root
of those who are trying to change the national regime.
- [June 24, 1932]
- Commander General of Division 1
has been assigned to visit provinces in the south
since June 15.
During this time,
high-ranking soldiers who are still in the city
including Ministry of Defense' Deputy Chief of Staff,
Army Area Commander,
and Chief of Staff for Royal Thai Army
are not staying in the city.
The members of royal family are not in the city
so we can control the soldiers easier.
Oh my goodness!
The sources reported that the soldiers from our side were arrested.
They were drunk and spilled our information
about trying to transform the nation.
What did you just say?
They didn't tell on us yet or it would be a warrant already.
But soon
they will spill the members of this movement for sure.
Phob, we don't have that much time. We need to do it.
The longer we wait,
the more information that the other side would get.
We need to do something to transform the nation.
Otherwise, we might not have another chance.
[The King and Queen's schedule to visit Klai Kangwong Palace.]
Phob? What are you looking for?
I…
Well…
I am looking for my document?
In my briefcase?
I thought that perhaps
you would accidentally pick up my document.
We've spent time together like all the time.
You're right.
That looks so good.
I brought you some snacks.
I'll clear it for you.
Come on, have a seat.
Here's your coffee.
Thank you.
Phob.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Did you heard the rumor
about a group trying to transform the nation?
Two soldiers were drunk and they spilled it.
I heard about it.
You need to be careful.
Don't be around this group ever.
My dad used to suspect you
and I didn't want youto be in danger.
Your Highness,
if one day
I did something terrible to you,
will you forgive me?
Why are you asking me this?
I'm just worried
that it could be something
to upset you in the future.
And you would leave me because of it.
I don't want that day to come.
Listen to me,
if you don't leave me
I won't leave you for sure.
When you were not around, I was so tortured.
I won't let it happen again.
You're working for the army?
What kind of liquor did you drink?
You were so drunk and said something so rebellious.
You shouldn't pay attention to little thing like this.
I told you already
that it was just a joke.
It is not real story.
Let's say that it was a joke,
like something you said among friends,
tell me, who are your friends to discuss it with?
Do you want me to bring you to the palace
so you will give me names?
Do you want to see miniter of interior?
Tell me, who are working with you in this disgraceful mission?
Tell me!
Write down the names.
You can still keep your head attached to your shoulders,
I will tell them to lower your penalty.
They won't spill anything.
I think we need to use harsher methods
to get them to speak.
They're so ungrateful to the nation.
I don't know what their plans are
but we need to be cautious.
Tinnakorn are leaving the city quite often.
I'm worried about him.
What? The Royal Palace Office
didn't have any work in the country lately.
None?
Well, I'm not sure.
Perhaps, they have to leave the city.
Otherwise, your son wouldn't tell you
that he needed to work in the country.
Phob!
It's not fair.
I was supposed to surprise you with it.
What?
Did you buy me a ring?
P T.
Phobthee.
Tinnakorn.
Phob, do you like it?
I asked them to make it special for us.
Of course, I do.
I really like it.
Thank you so much.
Phob! Oh!
Phob.
We will stay like this,
and be happy like this
forever.
- I want to call off the engagement with Ruethaisiri.
- Tin!
Get it together! Is it why
you don't want to get information from Prince Tinnakorn?
We should carry out the change in government on Friday, June 24.
The next two days?
Can you wait for me here
for the next two days?
Whatever happens
from now on,
please remember one thing,
I never meant to hurt you.
I know where your son is.